{
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Everthing in React is a ?",
        "choices": [
          "Module",
          "Component",
          "Package",
          "Class"
        ],
        "answer": "Component"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is ReactJS?",
        "choices": [
          "Server side Framework",
          "User-interface framework",
          "A Library for building interaction interfaces",
          " None of These"
        ],
        "answer": "A Library for building interaction interfaces"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of React.js Developer ?",
        "choices": [
          "Jordan mike",
          "Jordan Lee",
          "Jordan Walke",
          "Tim Lee"
        ],
        "answer": "Jordan Walke"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who Develop React.js?",
        "choices": [
          "Apple",
          "Facebook",
          "Twitter",
          "Google"
        ],
        "answer": "Facebook"
      },
      {
        "question": "ReactJS uses ___ to increase performance?",
        "choices": [
          "Virtual DOM",
          "Original DOM",
          "Both of above",
          "None of above"
        ],
        "answer": "Virtual DOM"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default port for webpack dev server??",
        "choices": [
          "3000",
          "8080",
          "3306",
          "8809"
        ],
        "answer": "8080"
      },
      {
        "question": "JSX is acronym for  ?",
        "choices": [
          "Java Server eXtension",
          "JavaScript eXtension",
          "Java Script Extender",
          "None of above"
        ],
        "answer": "JavaScript eXtension"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is bean in Spring ?",
        "choices": [
          "A component",
          "An Object",
          "A class",
          "A container"
        ],
        "answer": "An Object"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the basic concept of Spring ?",
        "choices": [
          "Factory pattern",
          "Singleton pattern",
          "Dependency injection or Inversion of control",
          "Abstract factory pattern"
        ],
        "answer": "Dependency injection or Inversion of control"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which spring module provides the capability of DI or IOC? ?",
        "choices": [
          "Spring web",
          "Core container",
          "AOP",
          "Data access"
        ],
        "answer": "Core container"
      }
      
    ]
  }